[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Damian] Tell Madam Red Dragon
to start looking for my replacement.
[Damian] This isn't the life
I want for my loved ones.
I don't want to be the Jaguar.
[Diego] We don't have any
control over the future.
But we have tonight.
I want to spend the rest of my life
with my best friend.
Will you marry me?
[Lily] I will. Yes, I'll marry you.
[Arnaldo] I'll give you tonight.
But, tomorrow
is a whole different story.
[Damian] I'm the Jaguar,
I worked for Red Dragon.
[Damian] Wait.
[Camia] Your uncle Damian
told me something.
[Lily] It all makes sense now.
Uncle Damian sacrificed a lot for us.
He's doing it for us.
[car door opens]
Get down!
[gunshots]
-Lily!
-[gun firing]
Lily! You bastards! Let Lily go!
[Julio] You did very, very good.
After everything that Lily Cruz
has put our family through,
she deserves to suffer!
[Jepoy] Anna?
Do you have news about
Lily and Auntie Camia?
Where are they?
[Anna] Jepoy.
[Jepoy] I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean it.
You didn't mean it?
You didn't mean to lie
and hurt me, huh, Jepoy?!
We don't know.
Then what are you still doing here?
Stop wasting your time
waiting around, Anna!
We're doing everything we can
to find them, Jepoy.
Don't take out your anger on us
because you're the one who's always away!
[Jepoy] I'm sorry, Anna.
Don't worry, I'll look for them.
Anna.
We have to go to the precinct
and get some updates.
[Marlon] You ready?
[tense music playing]
Where are Camia and Lily?
Come on, Jaguar…
[henchwoman] How should I know?
Where are they?!
Did you take them
to get back at me for leaving?
[henchwoman] What did you expect?
You know what we do to deserters.
You owe Red Dragon your life.
Now, if that Camia
and her daughter make you happy,
then I'm sorry to say they're
both probably six feet under.
You monsters!
I'm trying to change
for the better because of Camia.
If you hurt her…
…you'll have to deal with a Jaguar worse
than the one you first met!
[tense music swells]
[Diego] Psst!
[groans]
Hey. Where are they?
Huh!
Where are Lily and Camia?!
Answer me!
Ask Romulo! He knows where they are!
Where is he, then?
[tense music continues]
Where are they?!
[henchwoman 2] Boss Jaguar!
Answer me!
Romulo…
He knows where they are.
So where is Romulo?
[Julio] Where is that…
-…woman?
-[Helena] I can't wait…
-…to see her.
-That woman. Oh. There she is.
There she is.
-Speaking of.
-[Helena laughing]
[Julio] There.
Looking so helpless!
-Look at that.
-She looks… She looks like…
[Helena] The helpless Lily Cruz!
[Helena chuckles]
[Julio] Good morning!
-Good morning, Lily Cruz!
-[Helena laughing]
Good morning! Hi! You're awake!
Did you sleep well?
[Julio] How's your morning?
You're in handcuffs. Sorry about that.
Oh, there she goes.
So feisty!
[Julio] That's why I don't
like waking her up!
What is this about, Julio?
[Helena scoffs]
Where is my mother? Show me my mother!
-She's ballsy, isn't she?
-[Julio] I told you!
So you two are working together now?
Is this a new form of torture?
You know what? Just shoot me
and get it over with.
[Julio] How fearless!
Why are you in such a hurry to die?
[Julio and Helena] Oh!
What the hell is this, Emilia?!
[Emilia shushes]
[Helena laughs]
Mom! Mom! Mom!
[Julio] There's your mother.
Lily!
[Lily] Emilia, you monster!
-Drop that gun!
-[Emilia cackles]
Quiet! Quiet! Quiet!
Quiet! Keep your voice down!
I don't want to scare you but--
-[gunshot]
-[Emilia laughs]
You know what happens
when I panic? I shoot my gun!
[laughing]
-[gunshot]
-[Julio] Your daughter is nuts!
You're all insane, Julio!
Emilia, please…
Kill me. Leave my mother alone, please.
That's all I ask, Emilia!
Kill me and let my mother go!
Shut up!
-[Emilia laughs]
-[Helena] Typical.
Put the gun down!
Lily!
[whimpering]
Mom. Mom.
-[Helena] Here we go.
-[Camia] No!
Emilia, put your gun down!
-[shushes]
-[Lily] Just kill me, instead!
-[Helena] Chill!
-[laughs]
Mom.
-Lily! Don't!
-[Lily groans]
-[tense music playing]
-[no audible dialogue]
[screams]
[laughs]
[Camia] Lily!
-Ten, nine, eight…
-[Helena chuckling]
[Julio] …seven,
six, five, four, three…
two…
[Helena laughing]
She's out!
[Julio chuckling]
[Julio] That's how you shut her up.
-[Emilia] It's her turn now!
-Lily!
It's your turn, don't be jealous!
Do it now!
[tense music swells]
[Emilia] Ohhh! Enjoy!
[laughs]
[Emilia] Ah…
[Emilia howls]
[Emilia] I love it! Yes!
Sleeping time for these girls!
-Like mother, like daughter.
-Yes!
Knock out!
[Emilia] Party, party!
[Julio] Thank you. Oh!
Good morning, my queen!
Don't call me your queen.
Mmm!
Please?
Sit beside me, please. Or else…
[tense music plays]
Please?
There.
Now, that's better.
Okay.
Well, did you sleep well?
Actually, I did.
Wow! That's good. That's good.
I had the most wonderful dream!
Oh. Not that I'm interrupting, but
I did have a dream last night too.
What was your dream?
I dreamt that I was a real red dragon…
-[Julio] Oh.
-…with wings and all!
But then, I got attacked
by a group of peasants led by
that annoying Lily Cruz and her mom.
What did you do, then?
Well, I spit fire on them…
-Ouch!
-…and they turned into ash!
[both laughing]
What about you?
-[Julio] Oh.
-What did you dream about?
Well… Well, you know, I also had a dream,
but it wasn't as fantabulous as yours.
I dreamt about Romulo bashing
in the heads of Lily and Camia.
You know, you were there.
You were preparing the dinner table.
You were right beside the microwave oven
and you were about
to get their brains heated up
so we could have it for dinner with…
a very beautiful glass of wine.
Wow! Sumptuous! Very, very yummy!
And so, you see, my dear,
after all these years,
we still think alike.
And that's why you can't resist me.
Oh, that's not the only thing
I can't resist. This.
-Go get a room, please!
-Emilia, would you like me
to get a baby brother for you? Adopt one?
Unbelievable! No way! [groans]
[Emilia and Julio laugh]
[Emilia] Jen. Get me some water.
-Oh, well.
-This looks yummy.
[Damian groans]
[grunting]
I'm coming, Camia.
Not even death can stop me
from saving you.
[tense music swells]
Lily!
Lily! Lily!
Lily, dear!
[tense music swells]
[suspenseful music plays]
Let me out of here!
Let me go!
You bastards!
[Camia breathes heavily]
There's no point shouting.
No one will hear you anyway.
And don't do anything stupid.
Do you see those cameras?
We're watching your every move.
Don't even think about escaping.
Just accept what's about to happen to you.
You might end up liking it.
Don't touch me!
You're pretty.
-Don't touch me!
-Stop resisting. Come here.
Come closer.
There's nothing you can do now.
Come here.
[tense music plays]
[tense music continues]
[goon 3] Hey!
How did you get there?!
Go back there!
Get back there!
Stay still!
[grunts]
Untie me right now!
[gunshot]
[goon 3] Well?!
Do you want me to shoot you?
Just do as we say.
-Or you'll get hurt--
-[Ivy grunts]
Cut it out!
I'll shoot you!
Just do as we say!
It's like you want to get hurt.
[tense music continues]
[Romulo] Where's the other one?
[woman screams]
[people panicking]
[tense music playing]
You bastard!
[grunting]
[tense music swells]
Untie me!
[Helena chuckles]
[Helena laughing]
-[Julio] Whoa! [laughs]
-So feisty, this one!
[Julio] Hey there, Lily!
[Julio] Whoa.
You can wiggle and jiggle,
but you won't get out of there easily!
Where's my mother, old man?!
[Helena] Oh.
You will soon be reunited with your mom
in heaven.
Oh, Helena, stop it.
Don't be too presumptuous.
Lily Cruz here is not
a goody-goody gumdrop!
For all you know, she might
just end up going to hell.
The River of Hades!
[Lily] That's right!
I'll make sure we'll see each other there
because you'll go there first!
I'll get you first!
-[grunting]
-[Julio] Okay.
I am sure that I'm going to
enjoy hearing you scream.
-Oh my!
-[Helena and Julio chuckle]
[groans]
Goodbye, Lily Cruz.
Oh!
[Julio] Watch it! I told you she's feisty!
[Helena] You naughty girl. [chuckles]
Bye-bye!
[Helena] Bye!
[Lily] You have to forgive Helena.
She gets rowdy at times.
Excuse me.
Why did you let Romulo escape?!
He was our only hope
of finding Lily and Camia!
Don't blame this on me.
Why did you let him escape?!
If something happens to them,
I'll make you pay!
you'll be sorry!
[panting]
[phone rings]
Hello, Damian.
You…
I didn't take your resignation very well.
[Helena] In this industry…
…once you're in, the only way out
is death!
You monster! You're a monster, Red Dragon!
You're no better than me!
You want to change for the better?
Well, being good doesn't suit you.
Once a criminal, always a criminal.
You can't wash the blood stains
off your hands!
You know, your true self
will come out eventually.
And that time is now!
Where are Camia and Lily?!
Take me instead!
Don't drag them into this!
That's not going to be fun, is it?
What I want is for all of you to suffer!
I'll make sure you suffer first!
You and your whole family.
I've been a loyal soldier to you.
I sold my soul to the devil
because of you!
And this is what you do to me?!
Because you're an ungrateful bastard!
But, you know,
I like seeing this side of you.
I miss the old bloodthirsty Jaguar.
Stop trying to be a saint.
You're a criminal!
Bring back your old self.
Bring the Jaguar back!
Go to that place in 20 minutes,
or your precious love will die.
[laughs]
[screams]
[phone chimes]
[ominous choir music playing]
[Helena] Go to the place
I'll send in 20 minutes.
Or your precious love will die.
[ominous choir music continues]
[ominous choir music swells]
Damian.
[Camia] Damian.
[Camia panting]
[gunshot]
[suspenseful music playing]
No! Camia! Camia!
[chuckles]
Camia!
[tense music swells]
You won't die, Camia.
I'll do everything I can to save you!
[tense music continues]
[chuckles]
[phone rings]
Hello, bastard.
Damn you, Julio.
Let go of Lily and Auntie Camia!
Sure, sure.
But I want you to know,
it's not going to be easy.
What do you want from me?
What do you want from me?!
I'll be sending you
an address.
[Julio] And
you have to be there within
20 minutes of receiving it.
Because if not, if you arrive late
even by just a second,
your precious love…
will die.
Bye.
[tense music continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
Lily! Auntie Camia!
Auntie Camia!
Lily!
Lily! Auntie Camia!
[Diego] Damian!
Did they call you too?
Where are they?! Lily! Auntie Camia!
[suspenseful music continues]
Turn on the switch.
[wine pouring]
That's Dante Cruz! He's alive?!
He's not Dante.
That's his brother Damian.
-What?
-He is the real Jaguar.
Original Jaguar. I know.
And there's a fake one.
That's it!
So, that Damian is related
to Lily and Camia!
I get it now, Mama! I get it!
Yes, and that is why I love you so much.
-You're so smart, baby girl!
-[giggles]
Of course! I just knew
I always took after you.
And for sure, not from papa.
Where is that man, anyway?
The show is about to begin!
He's attending to some matters.
But he'll join us later.
I love you, grandson!
-Great!
-[Emilia] Hmm…
[Helena] Let's get the popcorn ready.
[static]
Now…
Where were we?
Let me go!
Why?
You know, Lily, I did not
come here to chat with you.
[Julio] I came here
to make sure you'll see
your loved ones' last moments.
[Julio] I want you
to watch them beg, suffer, and bleed!
And I want you to remember
that they're in that situation…
[tense music playing]
…all because of you!
You! Make her watch! Make her watch!
I want you to watch
each of your loved ones die
a slow, painful death!
[Lily] Make her watch! Watch, Lily Cruz!
We're about to watch
something spectacular!
[laughs]
Good day gentleman and pussycat!
[Helena on monitor]
I'm sure you recognize my voice.
I'm sure that you're
both searching for
the loves of your lives.
[Helena] The women you idiots
fell in love with!
[tense music continues]
[Lily] You monster… You monster!
-[Julio] Whoa.
-[Lily] Bastard!
[Julio] You exposed my knife!
What if I cut you into little pieces?!
But I don't wanna do that.
You have nice skin.
[laughs]
[Helena on monitor] But don't worry.
I'm gonna give them to you.
But only one of you will get
their heart's desire.
Now, let's see whose love is stronger.
Is it Damian's love for Camia?
[Helena] Or
is it Diego's love for Lily?
[laugh]
[Helena on monitor] How far
will you go for love?
Are you willing to kill
for that person you love?
[tense music swells]
[laughs]
[Julio] Like I told you, you can
try all night.
But, news flash!
You're never getting out of that chair.
You're never going to escape.
Because tonight, Lily Cruz--
"You're going to die, Lily Cruz!"
Yes.
"We'll kill you, Lily Cruz!"
"This is your last night, Lily Cruz!"
"Tomorrow, you'll be dead!"
Blah, blah, blah!
That's all I ever hear you say!
I even heard that from underground,
when you buried me alive!
But, what now?
I'm still here, very much alive!
That's a news flash for you,
Julio Ardiente!
-[Julio clicking his tongue]
-Lily Cruz is alive.
So, please stop threatening me,
because it's getting annoying!
[chuckles]
[Julio] Lily Cruz…
Lily Cruz and her far-reaching fantasies!
[laughs]
A fact I will tell you is
that all your loved ones
will die very soon.
But, there is this little detail
that I want you to remember.
My people aren't going to
kill them as you'd expect.
You know what's going to happen?
They're going to kill each other!
-[ominous choir music plays]
-[chains clinking]
[Helena on monitor] There's a gun hidden
somewhere in that warehouse.
And you have to find that gun and use it
against each other. Yes.
You want to be with your lovers?
[Helena] Then, you have to end
each other's life with a single bullet.
Then, you'll be with your beloved.
Damian. My favorite lieutenant.
If you kill Diego,
Camia lives. But, Lily dies.
And Diego. If you kill Damian, Lily lives!
But, that means
her noble mother, Camia, dies.
You monster!
[laughs]
[Helena] So, hmm?
What will it be? Let the games begin!
[tense music plays]
Happy hunting!
-[Helena] Cheers!
-[clinking]
[Emilia] Cheers! Cheers! This is it.
[tense music continues]
[Helena] Hey! Are you going to
stand there all day?
The game of death has begun!
What do you want?! A damn whistle?!
We won't give you what you want!
We're not going to kill each other!
Just give us back Lily and Auntie Camia!
Really?
Is that so, Diego?
Why don't you take a look
at that man beside you?
Why, isn't it my best minion, Jaguar?
If you only knew
the things Jaguar has done…
Despicable is an understatement.
[Damian on monitor] Do you think
I'm stupid, Red Dragon?
You don't have any proof
that you have Camia and Lily!
Of course, Damian.
You've got a criminal mind.
But don't you forget…
I am the leader. You are just a minion.
I'm two steps ahead of you.
[snaps] Monitors, please.
[Lily on monitor] You monsters!
-Let me out of here!
-Lily!
Camia! Red Dragon
you monster!
You criminals! Give them back!
What do you want?
Two cold, lifeless corpses in your hands?
[Helena chuckles] Now, move it!
Eight hours!
I'm giving you eight hours
to kill each other
in cold blood.
If neither of you dies within eight hours,
Lily and Camia
will both die.
And I'll kill the both
of you too so you can all burn in hell!
Come on, fighters!
Fight to the death!
Fight for your survival!
Fight for the survival of your witches!
Find the damn gun and give me
some red, hot, sticky blood!
[Diego] Eight hours.
We only have eight hours left. Come on!
[tense music playing]
[laughing]
Cheers, mama!
-Cheers!
-Oh, this is so exciting!
Blood for blood, Lily Cruz.
You know, Lily Cruz your veins
will bleed dry
if Damian kills that bastard Diego.
But if he doesn't,
then Camia Cruz, your mother,
will swim in her own blood
if Diego the bastard kills Damian.
See?
Now isn't that brilliant?
Come on, Lily. You have to give us that.
Uh-oh. Relax, relax.
You might hurt yourself.
Now. A question.
How?
How will the great Lily Cruz
get out of this dilemma
she brought upon herself?
Now, may I ask you, Lily.
Who's the idiot now?!
[laughs, spits]
[tense music continues]
[Diego] Hey, Damian!
[clanking]
Damian! Get moving!
Hey! Damian, do something!
[tense music swells]
Camia! Camia!
[Diego] Hey! What are you doing?
Listen to me.
Don't listen to Red Dragon.
She's manipulating us!
We can't let her get to us.
We'll work together. Let's go.
No, Diego.
-[Diego on monitor] Hey!
-That's it! That's it, Damian!
Kill Diego! Kill him!
[Helena chuckles]
We need to move. We need to move!
Come on! Snap out of it!
Arnaldo, who are you betting for?
Wrong question.
It's who I'm betting against.
[laughs] I bet it's Damian.
[Emilia] Because no matter
how much Lily Cruz hurt you,
you're still head over heels for her.
-Love, love, love.
-Yeah, yeah.
I fell in love, okay?
But love kills. You know?
Sometimes, you'd rather lose
the person you love along
with the person they replaced you with.
-[Emilia scoffs]
-Right?
Like you.
If dad was there fighting for his life,
would you bet on him?
[Helena] More popcorn.
We need to move.
Let go of me!
What?!
No matter how much you try
to find a way out,
it won't change a thing.
What are you saying?!
Use your head!
I know Red Dragon!
She does everything she says!
She doesn't joke around!
Look! Look around you!
She has eyes everywhere!
You think she'd let us escape?
So what?! We'll just let them die?!
Do you think we can get
out of here alive?!
Listen to me.
We need to work together to save them.
Do you understand?
Diego. This isn't a dream.
Wake up! Time's running out!
Seven hours! What are we going to do?
If we don't do anything,
Lily or Camia will die!
Put that in your head!
Only one of them can survive!
And only one of us can die!
And that's you!
[grunting]
Yes! The man is a beast!
Damian!
You're going to die.
-We're on the same side!
-Say your prayers!
-Go!
-Their group is falling apart
because they're turning on each other.
-[Emilia cheering]
-And all for Lily Cruz!
[Emilia chuckling]
[Helena] Emilia.
We'll finally get revenge for
everything she put you through.
-Yes.
-Victory is sweet!
-Whoo!
-Yes!
[Emilia laughing]
[Julio] Do me a favor.
Choose one. Right now.
But just one. Be honest.
Who do you want to win?
Or… who do you want to live?
Diego, who was the reason
you drove my grandson insane…
Or your beloved mother, Camia?
Choose. Choose well, my dear.
[Julio sighs]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[chuckling]
What's funny?
We've been fighting for a long time,
and yet you still don't know
who you're going up against?!
Moron!
[Lily] For your information…
You'll never defeat me!
You never will!
What I fight for,
Julio Ardiente, means something.
And all the ones I care for
believe in the same thing I do!
[Lily] They know how to be brave
and how to be smart!
So, I know they won't kill each other!
[tense music swells]
And I can assure you…
Your days are numbered, old man!
[laughs]
Your eyes are about to pop out.
[grunting]
[Emilia] That's it! Come on! Yes!
-Go!
-[Emilia] Game!
[Emilia laughs]
[chokes]
[Arnaldo] Oh. Oh.
-Hey. Are you okay?
-Give me some water!
-[Arnaldo] Water. Here.
-[Emilia coughing]
I got so excited! Oh, not that.
[Emilia] Hurry.
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[birds chirping]
[henchman] Boss. Lily Cruz?
What does she have to do with us?
Why do we have to save her?
Just do as I say.
I don't think that's fair, Jaguar.
You leave us to conduct
operations on our own.
You don't show up often,
and this is what we get from you?
Lily Cruz is an influential person.
She'll be indebted to us
once we win her trust.
That's why we need to do this, understand?
But, Jaguar, someone
more powerful wants to hire us.
And, I think, they're more
influential than Lily Cruz.
You know, you're getting on my nerves.
What are you getting at?
Who are you talking about?
Do you accept Lady N's offer?
Good to hear!
This is your first paycheck.
For joining us.
We are pleased to be of service to Lady N.
To tell you the truth, Jaguar,
we already made a deal with her,
and I and my men
will start working for her now.
I'm sorry, Jaguar. It's just business.
Nothing personal.
Till we meet again.
Let's go.
[tense music continues]
-[phone ringing]
-Oh, speak of the devil.
Hello, Raul.
Emilia!
[Raul] Where are you?
I am somewhere in between
"what do you care?"
and "mind your own business".
Calm down, Emilia.
I just called because I missed you.
Do you want me to pick you up?
Why don't we go out?
I mean, if you love someone,
you'll do anything for them, right?
Okay, fine. Let's meet up.
I'll see you.
Men are so needy nowadays!
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
Damian! Listen to me!
If you kill me, then it'll be
like you killed Lily too!
We're talking about your niece here!
[yelling]
All my life, I've always ended up losing!
I always make sacrifices!
I always compromise!
[grunting]
But if you kill Lily, tell me,
how will Camia ever love you?
I've lost Camia lots of times before!
I won't let that happen again!
In the end, it's us who will survive!
[grunting]
[tense music swells]
[Raul] You're telling me
that Diego's missing?
[Raul grunts]
Everyone has their secrets,
Raul. Deal with it.
[Julio] My henchman is
pulling down his pants zipper
because he's going to rape your mother!
[Lily] I will end you, Julio Ardiente!
You and your family will perish!
[Julio] And this will make you shut up!
[groans]
[Damian] I'm looking for the gun
that will kill you!
Instead of yapping,
why don't you look for the gun,
so you can save Lily?
Looking for this?! Are you ready to die?
[gunshot]
[theme music playing]